let me share with you a couple of
examples of how companies have leveraged
digital and gotten early so one of the
companies had the fortune of working was
icc lombard i used to work early days
where karthik jain and amit madan were
part of the team
and
they had a vision
that they want to take all their
business to digital
but they started small we started with
file activities and one spend went to
cross rupees a month and what they did
was they believed in content creations
we helped them develop a lot of content
we had them get their search strategy in
place they invested in seo they made
sure that every single touch point of an
experience of a customer to buy any
product or service from them was
simplified they got the call center in
order a lot of people would actually not
buy insurance online but what they did
was they said okay these are 20 steps
required to buy insurance offline in
digital we need only three steps how do
we make sure that three becomes two
becomes one
so if you take the last five to ten year
journey of i say lombard i think it's
one of the companies that has done
phenomenally well of transitioning
from that agent kind of a relationship
of shedding insurance to actually going
online and it's been an awesome journey
i've been proud to be a part of it